<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Avengers Data</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/data/</guid>
      <description>Iron Man
Descripcion Altura 6 feet, 1 inch Peso 225 pounds Weaknesses   Ego  Heart Issues  Strength   Intellect  Technopathy  Super Human Reflexes  Thor
Descripcion Altura 6 feet, 6 inches Peso 640 pounds Weaknesses   Short Tempered  Emotional  Strength   God of Thunder  Invulnerability  Captain America
Descripcion Altura 6 feet, 2 inches Peso 220 pounds Weaknesses   His Past  Emotions  Strength   Reflexes  Slowed Ageing  Super Healing  Hulk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COMMUNICATION CLIENT SERVER</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/comunicacionweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/comunicacionweb/</guid>
      <description>PARTIES INVOLVED Server Side  Server-side programming is a processing of a user&amp;rsquo;s request by interpreting a script on the web server to dynamically generate HTML pages as a response.
  Client Side  Client-side programming is the way that web pages manage events, make requests to the server and make simple validations and it is integrated into the HTML code
  Ajax Request  It is not a programming language but a tool to communicate the client side with the server side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Definiciones</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/definiciones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/definiciones/</guid>
      <description>Babel WebPack Prototype Polyfill    Prototype is a framework written in JavaScript that is oriented to the simple and dynamic development of web applications.
webpack is an open source JavaScript module package, used to generate static files representing those modules
Babel and Polyfill are tools that help to modernize our code
 PHP Frameworks from php    PHP is a programming language designed to develop applications for the web and create web pages, favoring the connection between servers and the user interface.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
